ybonline.co.uk 2015-09-07

# Use of Cookies | Yorkshire Bank

A cookie is a small file which is sent to your browser and stored on your computer's hard disc and helps us understand and track your use of the site and where it can improve the information and services provided.

There are two different categories of cookies:

**Session cookies** \- these are temporary and are erased when you close your internet browser.

**Persistent cookies** \- these remain on your hard drive until you erase them or they expire at a pre-set deletion date.

### The types of cookies we use on our website

**Cookie Type** | **Details**  
---|---  
Strictly necessary cookies | 

These cookies enable services you have specifically asked for.

They are essential in order to enable you to move around the website and use its features, such as accessing secure areas of the website. Without these cookies services you have asked for, like forms and internet banking, cannot be provided.  
  
Performance cookies | 

These cookies collect anonymous information on the pages visited.

These cookies collect information about how visitors use a website, for instance which pages visitors go to most often, and if they get error messages from web pages. These cookies don’t collect information that identifies a visitor. All information these cookies collect is aggregated and therefore anonymous. It is only used to improve how a website works.  
  
Functional cookies | These cookies remember choices you make to improve your experience. These cookies allow the website to remember choices you make (such as your user name, language or the region you are in) and provide enhanced, more personal features. These cookies can also be used to remember changes you have made to text size, fonts and other parts of web pages that you can customise. The information these cookies collect may be anonymised and they cannot track your browsing activity on other websites.  
Targeting or Advertising Cookies | These cookies are used to deliver adverts more relevant to you and your interests. They are also used to limit the number of times you see an advertisement as well as help measure the effectiveness of the advertising campaign. They are usually placed by advertising networks with the website operator’s permission. They remember that you have visited a website and this information is shared with other organisations such as advertisers. Quite often targeting or advertising cookies will be linked to site functionality provided by the other organisation such as advertisers.  
  
We may work with third parties to research certain usage and activities on our website on our behalf. No personal information about you is shared except to the extent it is required to be used by a third party or parties for providing such research, and in the course of conducting this research we, and/or these third parties may place a unique "cookie" on your browser.

We may also use web beacons or spotlight tags. These are transparent image files used to understand how users interact with the pages and content on the pages of our web site. We do not use web beacons to collect information about specific users.

We do not capture or record any personally identifiable information, with the exception of that stored in certain cookies used for analysis during the application process for products on this website. Any information that we collect and share is anonymous and not personally identifiable. It does not contain your name, address, telephone number, or email address.

### Specific Cookies

**Cookie** | **Purpose** | **Reference**  
---|---|---  
cbonline.co.uk  
ybonline.co.uk  
tracking cookie | Used to recognise repeat visitors to the site and in conjunction with other information we hold to attempt to record specific browsing information (that is, about the way you arrive at the site, pages you view, options you select, information you enter and path you take through the site) against an individual customer profile. |    
Redeye | We use Redeye's software to carry out statistical analysis of page use, page interactions and paths through CBOnline.com and YBOnline.com. This is known as 'web metrics'. This information allows us to more accurately understand our visitors’ browsing preferences. | [Redeye Cookie Policy](http://www.redeye.com/about-us/cookie-policy/)  
Google Analytics | These cookies are used to collect information about how visitors use our site. We use the information to compile reports and to help us improve the site. The cookies collect information in an anonymous form, including the number of visitors to the site, where visitors have come to the site from and the pages they visited. | [Google Analytics Cookie Policy](http://www.google.co.uk/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html)  
DoubleClick | We use pixels, or transparent GIF files, to help manage online advertising. These GIF files are provided by our ad management partner, DoubleClick. These files enable DoubleClick to recognize a unique cookie on your Web browser, which in turn enables us to learn which advertisements bring users to our website. The cookie was placed by us, or by another advertiser who works with DoubleClick. | [DoubleClick Cookie Policy](http://www.google.co.uk/intl/en/policies/privacy/)  
Adobe SiteCatalyst | These cookies are used to collect information about how visitors use our site. We use the information to compile reports and to help us improve the site. The cookies collect information in an anonymous form, including the number of visitors to the site, where visitors have come to the site from and the pages they visited. | [Adobe Privacy Policy](http://www.adobe.com/uk/privacy/analytics.html)  
Adobe Test & Target | Test & Target is used to optimise and personalise certain pages on our website. We use cookies to control various experiences which may be shown to customers in a randomised pattern in order to develop better user experience journeys for our customers. No personally identifiable information is recorded. | [Adobe Privacy Policy](http://www.adobe.com/uk/privacy/analytics.html)  
  
**For information about blocking the use of cookies, please refer to the instructions/help screen on your Internet browser. Detailed guidance on deleting or controlling cookies is available at[www.AboutCookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/).**

### Consent

By using our website you consent to our use of cookies.

You can manage your cookies within your browser settings however turning these off may impact your experience on our website.

### More Information

Please be aware that some aspects of our website, such as Internet Banking, will not work properly if you choose to not accept cookies via your browser.

Detailed guidance on deleting or controlling cookies is available at [www.AboutCookies.org.](http://www.aboutcookies.org/)
